<roomList>
    <room roomNum ="0" roomName="meadow">
        <desc>
This is the starting meadow. Butterflys float about as golden rays of 
sunshine cascade through the tree's leaves. You feel warm and sleepy.
a path into the forest is to your west. A Wooden post at the entrance reads &quot;to the plains &quot;
To your north, a castle surrounded by snow tipped mountains looms on the horizon.
Dunes of sand lie to your East.
A chilly wind escapes the entrace to a cave to your South.</desc>
        <items>
            <item name="sword">A Rotting Wooden sword, it&apos;s handle is well worn from years of novices practicing with it. It&apos;s blade is infested with moss</item>
        </items>
        <exits>   N  E  S  W   U   D
            <exit>1, 4, 5, 3, -1, -1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>


    <room roomNum ="1" roomName="Castle">
        <desc>
The Castle is surrounded by a moat. The Drawbridge is stuck halfway up. A lever on your side of the Moat is missing a gear.
A scraggly rockface that leads to an overlook looks easily climbable. 
The path to the meadow sits behind you to the South" </desc>
        <items> </items>
        <exits>
                   N   E  S   W   U   D
            <exit>-1, -1, 0, -1,  2, -1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>


    <room roomNum ="2" roomName="Overlook"> 
        <desc>
A gust of wind almost knocks you off your feet as you climb onto the overlook.
you can see the meadow to your south, and can see over the castle&apos;s ramparts. There is no 
movement in the bailey aside from a stray cat that skimpers toward the barn.
You can climb Down back the way you came.</desc>
        <items>
        <item name="telescope">A telescope. It&apos;s eyepiece is cracked. It needs to be repaired. "</item>
        </items>

        <exits>
                   N   E   S   W   U   D
            <exit>-1, -1, -1, -1, -1, 1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>


    <room roomNum="3" roomName="Plain">
        <desc>
A vast plain of rolling hills stopping only to meet the horizon lay infront of you. 
Speckled cows are scattered about, munching on the waving tall grass that sways in the wind.
There is a small cabin on one of the closer hills furthur to the West.
The trail to the meadow winds into the forest to your East </desc>
        <items> </items>
        <exits>
                   N  E   S   W   U   D
            <exit>-1, 0, -1, -1, -1, -1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>

    <room roomNum ="4" roomName="desert">
        <desc>
An airid desert lies before you. you&quot;ll need a camel and water to cross it. 
The meadow is to your West."</desc>
        <items> </items>
        <exits>
                   N   E   S  W   U  D
            <exit>-1, -1, -1, 0, -1, -1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>


    <room roomNum ="5" roomName="cave"> 
        <desc>
"The cave is damp and dark. You can only go so far before you can&apos;t see.
You&quot;ll need a torch to go furthur.
The Meadow is to the North."</desc>
        <items> </items>
        <exits>
            <exit> 0, -1, -1, -1, -1, -1</exit>
        </exits>
    </room>


</roomList>

